Hello, my friends.  Another day, another
life to save.  Coach Lil here again, my
friends.  And now I will share with you
six reasons why the
Manuel Life Freedom Product is the
best guaranteed investment
product today.
First, better coverage.
Your life insurance coverage is 200%.  You have life
insurance, your
family is protected from anything that happens to you.
The coverage is twice because you deserve
better, my friends.  Second, better
guarantees.  Guaranteed payout every
2 years.  You have a guaranteed income during
your retirement years.  The client doesn't have to
die or get sick for
you to enjoy your insurance.
You will receive a 10% payout coming from
your face amount.  For example,
your face amount is Php10 million.
You will have a Php1
million payout every 2 years.  Third,
better riders.  You can add a
critical illness rider, daily
hospitalization rider, and other riders
you need to make
your insurance coverage more comprehensive.
Fourth, better flexibility.  It's flexible
and you can
customize it.  You can choose the
coverage and payment terms that suit
your needs.  You can make it
monthly, quarterly, semi-annual or
annual.  You can choose.  The one that
really fits your budget, guys.  Fifth,
better maturity.  You don't have to
wait until you're 100 years old for
your plan to mature.  You can
choose to have your maturity after 20 years or during age
65 upon your retirement
.  So that even if you are alive,
you can enjoy
100% face amount of your product.  And
sixth, a better pension plan.
We can add that to
your manual life
freedom product with the perfect combination that will allow you to receive
a monthly payout and a separate annual
payout so that
your everyday life will be even better when you retire.
You can possibly have an estimated
monthly payout of Php9,000 monthly and
Php3,000 annually for lifetime benefits by
just saving
Php5,000 every month for 10 years.  So, my
friends, invest in Money Life
Freedom.  What you open is protected,
your life is protected, and you still have a payout
.  Don't forget to like, share and
comment.  And if you're ready to invest
now, just message me on my
messenger, I'm ready, coach L, so
we can discuss the
retirement plan in detail, see
[Music]